blackfive.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy | BlackFive

  * Blackfive.com Limited ("BlackFive", “us”) is committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and customers. The BlackFive team members are customers themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. This Privacy Policy describes the kinds of information BlackFIve collects about you and your use of the site and what we do with that information.

1\. Information Collection

We collect information from you in several different ways on this Site. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your personal information to:

· help make the Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.

· help you quickly find information, products, and services.

· help us create content that is most relevant to you.

· alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.

In order to keep you informed about our latest products, specials, and other news, we ask for your e-mail address. More importantly, we need this address should we need to contact you about any order, delay, or shipping information. To fulfill your order, we need your shipping address, phone number, and credit card information. We understand that we are asking for sensitive information, and you can rest assured that we make every effort possible to ensure the privacy and security of your transactions. Your personal data will be treated with the highest grounds of security and confidentiality, and we will not share your personal information with any third party without your consent.

In addition to personal information, we collect information about your visits to and use of the site that is not personally identifiable. For example, our site uses cookies, which are small information files that are sent to your computer and stored on your hard drive. Cookies ease your use of the site, and provide us with information about your use of the site – for example, the pages that you view. If you have registered with us, then your computer will store an identifying cookie which will save you time each time you re-visit the BlackFive site, by remembering your email address for you when you interact with the site. You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer without your explicit consent, but if you do not permit your browser to accept cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of the features of the site. We may also collect the IP address through which you access the Internet to use our site. Your IP address will typically be provided by your Internet service provider, your employer or the business or institution that provides you with access to the Internet. An IP address is not, by itself, personal information. We may use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which you and other guests visit the sites, and the patterns of site use. We may also combine IP addresses with personal information. To the extent that your IP address is combined with personal information, it will be treated as personal information. The site may also collect non-personal information through other technical methods.

2\. How we use Personal Information

Except as described below, we will not sell, rent, license or transfer your personal information to any third party.

We may provide your personal information to third parties who assist us in providing services to you, including fulfilling orders placed through the site – for example, shippers, warehouse operators, customer service providers, credit card issuers, or others involved in fulfilling orders you place on the site, or in responding to inquiries you make through the site.

We may also use your personal information to send you promotional materials about goods and services we offer. If you have made a purchase from our store we may occasionally update you on our latest products, news and special offers via e-mail, post & telephone. You will also be given the opportunity to receive such communications from us and selected third parties when you become a member of BlackFive. These materials and information may be sent to you by postal mail, e-mail or other means. As described below, you may opt out of receiving these communications.

We may also take personal information and make it non-personally identifiable. We may, for example, remove information from your personal information that does not identify you - for example, your age or gender – or we may combine elements of your personal information that do not identify you with non-personal information of other users of our site. Our use of this depersonalized or aggregated information is not restricted.

3\. How Secure Is Information About Me?

The security and confidentiality of your information is important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect personal information from unauthorized access and improper use. 

· We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

· We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

· It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

4\. Are Children Allowed to Use the Websites?

The Websites do not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use the Websites only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

5\. Third party sites

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they may have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

6\. Privacy policy updates

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or contacting you directly via email or other means. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website after such changes have been first posted. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: service@blackfive.com
